BRANDON OCCHIUZZI

8 Valley Drive, Bracebridge, Ontario, P1L 1B8 Telephone: 705-380-6180 | Email: bocchiuzzi@hotmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a versatile, results oriented professional who has had administrative, marketing, and negotiatio n experience as part of my management and account management experience in the food and beverage i ndustry. I have excellent interpersonal, organizational, and time management skills as well as a keenly d eveloped cultural sensitivity due to my extensive travel experience.

KEY SKILLS

- Outstanding sales proficiency.
- Excellent interpersonal skills with strong conflict resolution abilities.
- Demonstrated proficiency in accomplishing performance objectives.
- 20 years of experience in the customer service industry in many different styles of service and management.
- Able to type 70 WPM, proficient in Microsoft Word, Excel, Outlook, and PowerPoint.
- Strong leader and team player with exceptional communication skills.
- Self-motivated, accountable, creative, and coachable.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts - Classical History | Nipissing University | 2008

Ontario Secondary School Diploma | Huntsville High School | 2004

RECENT WORK EXPERIENCE

PELEE ISLAND WINERY, Sales Representative

2017 - 2020

- Responsible for selling, marketing and providing education with regards to the winery's portfolio
 to LCBOs and licensees across the largest territory in Ontario (north of Highway 89, all the way
 up to Sault Ste Marie and Timmins).
- Identifying and securing new accounts and avenues of sale while continuing to expand and provide exceptional service to existing clients.
- Successfully managing my time, both on the road and at my home office, in order to efficiently perform my job duties.
- Responsible for maintaining accurate sales data, account information, delivery instructions and schedules.
- Demonstrated ability for reading, interpreting and successfully acting upon sales trends.
- Organizing and resolving issues with office staff, clients, LCBO managers, fellow sales reps, and prospective clients almost exclusively via phone and email.

BARRIE COUNTRY CLUB, Food and Beverage Supervisor

2014 - 2017

- Participated in the hiring process from candidate selection through to interviews and on boarding.
- Overseeing and providing support to formal, corporate and member events of up to 300 guests.
- Leading and supervising a busy food and beverage team.
- Ensuring member and guest needs are both met and exceeded on each and every visit.

THAT LITTLE PLACE BY THE LIGHTS, Supervisor & Bartender/Server

- 2012 2014
- Applied strong multi-tasking skills while bartending, managing staff, wait list and reservation list.
- Resolved any issues that arose between staff on shift or with guests of the restaurant.
- Utilized time management and interpersonal skills to ensure the restaurant ran smoothly and that all guests received excellent customer service.

THE BOARD OF TRADE COUNTRY CLUB, Supervisor / Manager

2013

- Communicated daily with management team through administrative reports and management
 meetings regarding labour costs, employee evaluations, member and employee issues, pricing,
 events, inventory counts, and other administrative duties.
- Responsible for daily operations of the club restaurant.
- Provided leadership and management to the food and beverage team.
- Resolved conflict and issues between guests and employees quickly.
- Ensured guest needs and satisfaction were met and exceeded on each and every visit.

C.I.A LANGUAGE SCHOOL, SOUTH KOREA, ESL Teacher

2009 - 2010

- Taught English as a second language to adults and children.
- Demonstrated ability to communicate clearly and concisely, as students ranged in proficiency from almost no language skill to high proficiency.
- Organized lesson plans and class schedules.

Other Customer Service Work Experience

Bartender/Server

Boston Pizza	Huntsville, ON	2015
Grandview Golf & Country Club	Huntsville, ON	2014
The Cottage Waterfront Bar & Grill	Huntsville, ON	2014
The Grand Pizzeria and Bar	Ottawa, ON	2012 - 2013

Duties and Responsibilities:

- Utilized time management and interpersonal skills to provide excellent customer service in fast paced environments.
- Resolved conflict and issues quickly and effectively.
- Responsible for bar inventory and organization.

REFERENCES

Manny Buttus | Owner, That Little Place by the Lights | 705-783-9306

Winston Barrett | Owner & Chef, Chez Michele | 705-305-9561